(Watch on KonFlix.vip)
MY ROYAL NEMESIS
Here we go.
Try a little harder this time.
At this rate, I will win again.
Please take it easy, Your Highness.
We do not want a stray arrow to ruin
all the beautiful peonies.
-Do you find them beautiful as well?
-Yes.
I was right to clear the patch
and plant peonies.
When it comes to flowers,
they need big heads like this
to be worth looking at.
A peony, beaded with dewdrops
like pearls, was plucked…
by a beauty as she passed a window.
With a smile, she asks her beloved,
"Which is fairer, the flower or I?"
The young lord answers
in gentle mischief.
"The flower is far fairer."
I, too, find the peonies
more beautiful than Your Majesty.
I can never win against you.
No flower in the world could be
as beautiful as you.
Your Majesty.
It is time for your midday meal.
What brings you all the way to the Annex?
I have
a gift for you.
Your Majesty, what is this?
Your health seems
to have declined of late.
I personally asked the Royal Infirmary
to concoct you a restorative tonic.
A restorative tonic…
Royal Consort Hui of the Kang clan
shall accept the poison.
Royal Consort Hui,
what is the meaning of this?
Your Majesty, please take the tonic away.
I cannot stand
even the smell of tonic.
Hey, Ms. Shin Seo-ri.
Ms. Shin Seo-ri, wake up.
The shock must've been too much.
I'll call an ambulance.
No, this isn't
just another minor fender bender.
The media may exploit this.
-Call Dr. Kim.
-Yes, sir.
Wait.
Ms. Shin, are you awake?
EPISODE 2
A GUIDE TO OPTIMIZING YOUR FATE
Given that he resides
in such lofty chambers,
he must be
at least a high-ranking minister.
He has the pedigree, influence,
and even that handsome face.
He truly has it all.
How did you know
a mannequin would fall from the sky?
I just knew.
My instincts in that sphere
are exceptionally keen.
Damn it.
Arrest that assassin at once!
What are you waiting for?
Seize her this instant!
Take him into custody immediately!
I am endowed
with a remarkably keen sixth sense.
It has allowed me to survive
countless attempts
of poisoning and assassination.
Thanks to me, you have preserved
your precious life.
Don't tell me.
Were you in on it?
Are you implying I am involved
with those schemers
who lower themselves to using assassins?
I never scheme from the shadows.
I strike necks openly.
So you're not one of them,
but you just happened to pass out
in front of my car and save me today?
I think I get the gist of it.
I'll have Mr. Son compensate you
for your troubles. You may leave now.
Now, hold on.
Do you take me for some beggar,
groveling for scraps?
You are not as perceptive as you appear.
I have something
that you desperately need.
Hence, I was going to give you
the chance to make a deal with me.
You want to make a deal with me?
Even with all these subordinates
at your feet, your life hangs by a thread.
What use are absolute power
and worldly riches?
Before a fleeting life,
even the supreme sovereign's throne
is but vanity.
I shall safeguard
the flickering flame you call your life.
Keep me by your side.
Unhand me at once!
Do you know who I am?
Unhand me!
Damn it.
How can you be
such a poor judge of character?
That pretty face has you
with your nose high in the air.
You deserve to be struck down
by lightning from the heavens above.
That's pretty harsh.
You would curse someone
who was just senselessly attacked?
I know Mr. Cha
can be a bit unreasonable at times,
but please bear with him.
Yes. He certainly is
an impulsive fool through and through.
Working for him must be torture.
Let's go, Ms. Shin. I'll take you home.
In this moving palanquin?
Hear me!
Shall we?
Mr. Cha, this is
the CCTV footage from the scene.
Why would they do this?
I thought it had already been handled.
Sir,
about that protester from earlier--
Can it wait?
I need to make a call.
Yes, sir.
Mr. Son.
Let's just handle the guy
from the lobby earlier.
How exactly?
You said it was about unpaid wages.
Just resolve it for them.
Is there someone behind the scenes?
Any guesses on the motive?
I assume it's money.
They attacked even after they were paid
what they were owed.
There's a bigger payout somewhere.
He just slammed the door in my face
as if I were some assassin.
What is he scheming now?
Is he having me watched? Is that it?
No, not at all.
Mr. Cha was worried about you.
He asked me to make sure
you got home safely.
He was worried about me?
When I reviewed your profile,
I noticed you lived nearby.
I mean, you were almost
in a car accident earlier.
And had the audition too.
You've been through a lot today,
so he was concerned.
In this desolate world,
I guess I have someone
who worries about me.
Too bad he is the cause of my distress.
Ms. Shin, are you okay?
You look a little pale.
Well, actually,
I have wanted to ask you this
for some time now.
Could you slow down a bit?
This palanquin is moving way too fast.
It is making me very dizzy.
But we're only going
20km an hour right now.
In all my life,
I have never been in a palanquin
that went this fast.
Father.
Is this seafood stew?
Seafood herbal chicken stew.
Made with 100% wild-caught abalone.
I took the first flight to Jeju Island
at the crack of dawn
just to get this for you.
-I didn't sleep a wink.
-You can be so silly.
Did you already forget
that Father caught that awful norovirus
from eating raw oysters
at his birthday last year?
You know he has a weak stomach.
What hearty roots.
Abalones are so basic.
You should have one before the meal.
It's genuine wild ginseng harvested
by a ginseng forager
on Mount Jiri.
It has a nice bitterness to it.
That's the real deal.
I can't compete with you two.
Next time you prepare a gift for Uncle,
can you include me?
Sure thing, Mun-do.
It's a bit rude to show up empty-handed
to your uncle's birthday party, no?
Don't talk to Mun-do about manners.
Ten kids don't compare
to one good nephew.
Here we go again.
That damn liver story.
17 YEARS AGO
All right, who's going to give me a liver?
If it weren't for this godforsaken asthma,
I would gladly give you as many pieces
of my liver as you wanted.
If I just weren't breastfeeding the kids,
I would gladly chop mine off for you.
I'll give you mine, Uncle.
While my perfectly healthy kids
turned their backs on me,
my nephew gave me a second chance at life.
And you brats can't even show
gratitude to your father's savior.
Uncle, please stop.
Se-gye was too young back then,
and the rest all had valid reasons.
All I had to offer was my health anyway.
Yes, I'm only alive
because of you, Mun-do.
What a shame.
How nice it would be if Se-gye
were even half the man you are.
DAEBAK BOARDING HOUSE
It appears I still had
surprises waiting for me.
Mr. Cha insisted
that you get checked out by a doctor.
The aftereffects of a car accident
really get you.
Make sure you go tomorrow.
After rebuffing me so harshly to my face…
He certainly is a man
riddled with contradictions.
What a destitute life this woman leads.
You call this a house?
I have arrived!
Look at that freak. She must be wasted.
Like she's a noblewoman or something?
-I know, right?
-Hey…
I have arrived!
Is anybody in there?
My word. Is this any way to treat
the master of the house?
What is the gatekeeper even doing?
That light turned on by itself.
Hold on…
I need to gather my wits about me.
Keep your wits about you,
and you can survive even a tiger's den.
"With a focused mind,
nothing is impossible."
Unit 203!
Where have you been?
Why are you getting back so late?
And why is your phone off?
Hurry upstairs. Your grandmother
has been waiting for ages.
Just to see your face.
Grandmother?
My goodness.
There's my little girl.
Come and sit down.
Sit. Go on.
You didn't even have time to change?
What is all this?
All right.
Here. Try this.
I made your favorites.
Japchae and pork cutlets.
I even made candied sweet potatoes.
Come to think of it,
I have not eaten all day.
I fried them myself.
They say a person's hands
reveal the life they have lived.
Why do you look so worn out?
It seems this woman's grandmother
did not have an easy life either.
Did work keep you from eating again?
Hurry up and eat.
Here, take these and eat.
Oh right.
You should join us for a bite too.
-Really? Yes. Thank you so much.
-Sure.
Thank you.
Silly me. How could I be so forgetful?
I'm on this herbal supplement, you see.
So I don't think
I should be eating all this meat.
But there's no meat in this.
No, I'm fine. Really.
Enjoy your meal, Unit 203.
-Excuse me.
-Sure.
Goodness.
Here.
Don't share this with anyone.
Hide it in a corner somewhere
and eat it all by yourself. Got it?
This isn't pork. It's beef.
High-quality Korean beef.
See. Korean beef.
Is it good? Do you like it?
You know, I've been messing up
the seasoning lately.
I put extra effort into this one.
It is quite delicious.
Really?
Gosh.
Great. Go on.
Eat up.
Go on now. Have some japchae too.
Have some more.
You must have been starving.
How nice it is to have
everyone gather for a meal like this.
Asking the family to gather
for a measly meal on my birthday
is not asking for the moon.
And yet, I don't even know
if the one grandson I have will show up.
Father, you saw the news, right?
I mean, he is way too old
to be acting out like that.
I guess he still can't control
that temper of his.
They say the video was doctored.
Looks like someone was messing with him.
He's probably late
cleaning up that mess, Uncle.
You sure know everything, don't you?
Fake or not, he should've
just behaved himself all along.
With that kind of reputation,
people will believe anything,
no matter how outlandish or tawdry.
Don't you agree, Father?
Why that little…
Happy birthday, Grandfather.
Sorry I'm late. Car trouble.
You should've planned ahead for that.
A businessman should be able
to manage his time.
I knew the party would start
with the usual catfight
and shameless displays of loyalty.
Neither of which I can stomach.
So I timed my arrival to avoid it.
Is it still going?
You rotten scoundrel.
Even at a birthday party,
you can't keep that trap of yours shut?
Please try to calm down, Uncle.
It's your birthday, after all.
Welcome, Se-gye.
Cheers.
Sir, the CCTV footage
from the rear entrance confirms
the attacker fled in a nearby getaway car.
It was parked too far away
for the cameras to catch the plate.
Just as I expected.
Which means it wasn't a random attack.
Sir, we should request
a police investigation now.
They timed their attack to coincide
with the buyer meeting and audition.
It appears they were targeting
the "abusive CEO" image.
That's why.
The intent was underhanded
and premeditated.
We can't just play into their hands.
Is there someone you suspect?
There's no shortage of people
who want to see me crash and burn.
I suppose you're right.
They all treat me like a thief
raiding the family vault.
The eldest aunt, the youngest aunt,
and even the distant cousin.
This place is crawling with fake smiles.
Seo-ri.
You're all alone in this strange place.
It must be hard.
I know how you feel.
My restaurant is doing well.
Stop worrying about me
and buy yourself some new clothes.
No young lady should be dressed like this.
You'll never land a fellow
looking like that.
As if having one ever leads
to anything good.
You grew up so lonely
without your parents' love.
You should have at least one person
on your side in this world.
But still, you grew up to be
such a fine young lady.
You've done such a great job.
I'm so proud of you.
Are you proud of your granddaughter?
Of course.
You're so beautiful inside and out.
In all my time on this earth,
I've never met anyone like you.
Hurry inside.
I'll be going now.
Go on.
Go inside.
Safe…
travels.
-Mr. Son.
-Yes, sir.
Twice can't be a coincidence, right?
Pardon?
Think about it.
She passed out in front of my car
when it was barely moving,
and then she predicted
that attack like some sort of psychic.
I looked into Ms. Shin Seo-ri.
Besides her rude speech,
nothing else seemed suspicious.
Surely you don't think
someone put her up to this?
It never hurts to be careful.
We've put everything on the line
for this brand launch,
even shouldering private fund risk.
We need to be
extra cautious right now.
Double the security team for now,
and personally double-check
all the HR files.
Yes, sir.
And find out
everything you can about her.
Yes, sir.
You call this a room?
A prison cell would be more luxurious.
What in the world…
Look here.
No window ought to command such a view.
Seriously? Were you expecting
a view of Namsan Tower or something?
Why are you complaining now?
It's compact and great value.
With ventilation, no less!
I gave you our most popular room.
You call this a room and collect rent?
I have never encountered
such miserliness in my life.
All the windowless rooms are taken now.
You can move when one opens up.
Wait.
There are even rooms without windows?
Unbelievable.
I never!
My goodness.
Why, this scoundrel…
Unit 203, open up!
Open this door!
Unbelievable.
Who goes there?
What sort of knave batters
a lady's door in the dead of night?
"Knave"? Seriously?
You know, I've tolerated
all your noise until now,
but I can't take it anymore!
You keep rustling around,
and you won't stop talking to yourself.
I can't live like this.
If you cannot live with that,
you should just leave.
Have you lost your damn mind?
Are you trying to start a fight with me?
You can hear every burp
and fart from your neighbors here.
Wouldn't it be common courtesy
to be a bit more careful?
What the… Hold on.
What's going on here?
What's with all this racket?
This man here is making
the most absurd complaints.
He says not to burp
or fart too loudly in my own room.
Why not just tell me
to stop breathing altogether?
Unbelievable.
You clearly missed the point.
We are trapped in this prison together.
If we cannot show a little grace
and forgive small faults,
how are we any different from beasts?
"Beasts"?
So are you saying
I'm some kind of savage now?
Mencius said
that a sense of shame and indignation
is the beginning of righteousness.
You fail to see your own flaws
and only harp on others.
Like a crap-covered dog
scolding a dusty dog.
Crap dog? You calling me a mutt?
-Hear, hear!
Who was that?
I ought to wring your neck,
but it seems
I have public sentiment on my side.
So stop causing a scene and begone!
My day has been long enough.
She couldn't even look me
in the eye before.
What's gotten into her?
I just sensed an assassin's presence.
Someone nearby is after your life!
Get down!
Keep me by your side.
I shall safeguard
the flickering flame you call your life.
As if she could keep anyone safe.
How truly marvelous.
This is pure witchcraft.
If you pull the string,
it lights right up.
How useful.
You tell me to leave because I am useless?
Do you think Court Lady Kim
took a bribe?
I cannot understand
why she brought in someone like you.
Who are you to decide my worth?
Look at the venom in her eyes.
Jumping into that river
must have been easy for you.
I heard you ran away
after being sold into slavery.
A lowly wench like you
should know her place.
How could we ever share a room
with someone like you?
-So vile.
-What did you say?
Did you just call me vile?
Looks like you grew up sheltered
and do not know any better.
Allow me to show you
what something truly "vile" looks like.
My goodness!
Just try calling me vile again.
I will pour it over your heads next time!
Have you lost your damn mind?
Grab her!
Let go of me! You cannot be serious!
The palace follows a set of laws.
Even the Inner Court's lowest ranks
have a hierarchy.
Let me give you a proper lesson
on those laws today.
You two, drag her out.
Let me go!
Let me out this instant!
Let me out!
Grab that rock.
Why is she so quiet?
I heard she was a little crazy.
What if something is wrong with her?
Who cares? She deserves it.
She should have just left
when we asked nicely.
Let us go.
Now I will not have to stay up
every night…
tending the lamp.
That scoundrel still has not come
to his senses.
I should have snapped his wrists
when I had the chance.
How will I ever
get any sleep with all this commotion?
YEONGHWI CHAMBER
Please let me out!
Just look at this household.
Not so much as a piece of gold
or a simple jade ring to be found.
I am an actor.
A former child star
who no one recognizes anymore.
I'm just a nobody with no ties
to the mythical rise of K-dramas.
Harder. One more.
-Cut! Turn it around!
-Let's turn it around.
Who is she?
Where did they even find her?
-Let's clean this up.
-Okay.
Hurry up.
WE'RE ROOTING FOR YOUR DREAMS
The world likes to admire dreamers…
BALANCE: 164,019 WON
…but even encouragement has its limits.
FUNDS TO WIRE TO NAM OK-SUN
50,000 WON
100,000 WON
TRANSACTION COMPLETED
GRANDMA
-Grandma.
-Hey, Seo-ri.
I just sent you some money.
So treat yourself to a nice meal.
Don't go asking around for scraps.
Gosh, I'm just an old lady.
I wouldn't even know where to spend it.
Hey, keep it down!
What was that noise?
Are you with someone?
No. That's just the TV.
You've got great hearing.
How did you even hear that?
My eyes and ears still work just fine.
I have to stay healthy
if I want to see you on TV.
Grandma, I'm going to make it big on TV.
You just wait and see.
Of course. I'm so proud of you.
My grandma always tells me
she's proud of me.
But whenever I hear that,
it makes me feel small
for some odd reason.
I'm just a burden of a granddaughter
who can't let go
of a dream that will never come true.
What is there to be proud of?
How has she made it this far
without earning any real money?
What a pitiful diary.
She wrote down every trivial detail,
as if it were something to be proud of.
No wonder every bastard she meets
tries to walk all over her.
SLEEP IS FOR THE DEAD
THE FUTURE LEADING LADY
YOU WILL BECOME A STAR
I WILL GIVE MY GRANDMA A GOOD LIFE
I'm so proud of you.
A peony, beaded with dewdrops
like pearls, was plucked
by a beauty as she passed a window.
No flower in the world
could be as beautiful as you.
"Royal Consort Hui of the Kang clan,
of the Inner Court,
has committed a heinous crime."
Royal Consort Hui shall come forth
and receive the royal command!
They say
no blossom endures its bloom forever.
The Three Obediences.
Obey your father.
Obey your husband.
And obey your son.
That is what is expected of women.
Rather than clinging pitifully
to a wretched life with no one to rely on,
perhaps death would be…
Better, my foot!
Even if I am wallowing in dog crap,
life is better than death.
So in this life,
I will do what I must to survive it.
That will also be how I honor the one
to whom this body truly belongs.
I will tell you all about it,
so try not to doze off
and listen well.
Whenever foreign enemies invaded,
the people always stepped up
to fight before anyone else.
-If they had no guns, they used swords.
-Gosh.
If they had no swords, they used rocks.
The country did nothing for them,
yet they still sacrificed
their precious lives.
Meanwhile,
due to treaties signed by a few traitors,
the country lost its sovereignty!
Those traitors deserve
to be torn limb from limb!
They should be torn to pieces!
Long live Korean Independence!
-Long live Korean Independence!
Long live Korean Independence.
Long live Korean Independence!
Long live!
Republic of Korea!
Hey! Hey, everyone!
Everyone, come out!
Come on, everybody!
Did you see the miracle
of the Red Devils?
We made the semifinals! The semifinals!
Republic of Korea!
What's her deal?
The semifinals were ages ago.
DAEBAK BOARDING HOUSE
Curse this wretched fate of mine.
I am stuck here washing clothes
like some lowly servant.
Curse this fate.
What the… blood!
There are rats everywhere I go.
Did you see that?
She just threw that bat at his head.
That was amazing.
SHIN SEO-RI
To the one coveting my side dishes,
I cast a death curse last night.
If you wish to avoid an untimely death,
return it to its rightful place.
Death curse, my foot.
Pork collar and jowl, here I come.
Got you now.
I knew it was you.
The containers look similar.
I just got confused for a second.
See. They all look alike.
Are your eyes attached to your feet?
Or are you just completely illiterate?
My name is clearly written on it.
How dare you feign ignorance?
-What's going on?
-He got caught stealing side dishes.
Did he steal
my leftover jokbal and whelk too?
What's wrong with you all?
Do you have any proof?
Do you?
Don't point fingers.
I can't believe this.
Now that I have caught the rat,
you may all rest easy
and partake of your meal.
Amazing.
Unit 203 just caught
the rooftop pervert too!
She threw that laundry bat
like a shot put.
I saw the whole thing.
No need.
I did nothing to merit such fuss.
BEST WISHES ON YOUR OPENING
CHOI MUN-DO, CHAIL E&C
Hey.
Jeong-hyeon.
Congratulations.
I should've come by sooner.
That was thoughtless of me.
Thoughtless? You sent a plant
and even some cash.
I shamelessly
and happily accepted them.
I thought you were only good
at caring for people,
but you're good with plants too.
Then again,
you've always been very attentive.
You even put up
with someone as finicky as Se-gye.
How is Se-gye doing these days?
A plant? That's so not him.
-Cash would've been better.
-Yeah.
He gave me some cash, too. Mun-do.
A cash gift for the clinic opening.
Nothing in life is free.
Free money always comes
with a high interest rate.
Don't worry.
As if Mun-do would ever do that.
Enough about me.
Let's go back to your story.
-What story?
-About that weird woman.
That woman in a shaman's hanbok
jumped in front of your car,
showed up at your company,
predicted that attack,
and she even offered to protect you?
What do you think her deal is?
She's really getting on my nerves.
Like a splinter under my fingernail.
Paranoia. Are you getting
enough sleep these days?
You know.
I had this weird dream the other day.
-Some woman appeared in it.
-Who?
I woke up before I saw her face.
But you know,
some of it actually made sense.
I was sleeping in a palace courtyard
in the middle of the day.
That would mean I was someone
of some standing, right?
So you're saying
you were a royal in your dream?
Should I buy a lotto ticket?
I feel like it had
some sort of hidden meaning.
No hidden meaning. Just a dream.
Stop chasing women in your dreams
and meet one in real life.
Damn it, why do you always end up there?
You just don't understand yet.
Love is the best medicine.
It's like a powerful shot of oxytocin.
Best medicine, my ass.
You quack.
NEWTUBE
ROYAL CONSORT HUI OF THE KANG CLAN
Okay.
The master of palace intrigue.
How did she get caught up
in all that palace intrigue?
The gangster royal consort.
The truth behind the poison refill.
What do these young punks know?
Damn it.
I should just eat.
He still has not learned his lesson yet?
Stealing side dishes again?
He deserves to die in his sleep.
Unit 203 is really laying down the law
and asserting her authority.
There's no kimchi either.
Hold on.
Should he not have sent word by now?
Forget it.
That degenerate treats me like I am a spy.
He can die for all I care.
Love is the best medicine.
It's like a powerful shot of oxytocin.
Medicine? More like poison.
Cha Se-gye!
Unhand me, you damned brutes!
What are you doing back here?
Damn it.
So, have you considered my proposal?
What proposal?
Oh, that ridiculous proposal
to protect me?
That is right.
I was unaware of your standing then
and acted a bit imprudently.
"A bit"?
Perhaps… more than a bit.
But now that I am fully aware
of your position,
I know your need for my services is
all the more urgent.
You claim to know me so well,
yet you barge in here so arrogantly?
Have you forgotten already?
I am the one who saved your life.
The least you could do
is show eternal gratitude.
You dare forsake your savior?
Oh man. "Savior"?
Stop spouting nonsense
about protecting me
and just ask for money.
The eye is just the mind, looking out.
Perhaps you, who only sees me
as a money-grubber,
are the one possessed by such a spirit.
"Possessed" is a bit much.
Let's go with "CM."
"See-em"?
I have never heard of such a word.
What does it mean?
It means…
Capitalist Monster. "CM."
That is what I am.
-A monster?
-Yeah, a monster.
Simply put, I could easily chew up
and spit out a little greenhorn like you.
So before things get ugly,
you should get out of here.
Why, you little scoundrel!
Ungrateful degenerate. Have you no grace
for those who show you concern?
What do you think you're doing?
Are you insane?
Don't just stand there! Drag her out!
What the--
Stop right there!
Do not flee from me!
Do you think you are invincible?
If you do not value your life,
you will meet an early end!
Assassins do not rest
once a target has eluded them!
Damn it.
It is not working.
He is one wicked creature.
As wicked as can be.
Damn it, she's clinging on
like some kind of vengeful ghost.
She's trying to use this fender bender
to change her entire lot in life.
This is all you could get on Shin Seo-ri?
How can someone's life be summed up
in less than a page?
I looked into her further,
but that was all I could find.
She experienced a brief flash
of fame as a child actor,
but no one recognized her
as an adult.
Perpetually stuck
between rookie and nobody, so to speak.
"Nation's Pebble"? Please.
More like a chunk of gravel.
Poor educational background,
a tragic family history,
and a string of part-time jobs…
It all makes sense now.
It does look like that on paper,
but strangely enough, in person,
she doesn't seem like the type
to have any ulterior motive.
She really did seem
genuinely worried about you.
They say it's easier to map the seafloor
than it is to map a person's intentions
for a reason.
Who knows when she'll show up
to cause a scene?
-Keep security as is.
-Yes, sir.
He has his subordinate escort me
because he's worried about me,
but to my face,
he treats me like a money-grubber.
And why does he get
so close for no reason?
I have never met someone
so two-faced in my lifetime.
I see. Your first time.
His life is in danger.
How can he remain so carefree?
"Do not wait until it is too late to act."
He will clearly need my help
sooner rather than later.
Yes. I see, Your Majesty.
Well…
I did not say anything earlier
because arguing about etiquette
from 300 years ago would be pointless.
But technically, I am not "Your Majesty."
I am "Your Highness."
Your Highness, Your Majesty, or whatever.
What difference does it make?
The class system was abolished
over a century ago anyway.
From what I have seen,
that is not entirely true.
The class system may be gone,
but inequality remains.
This is a world in which
the rich are able to exploit people
even easier, if anything.
All right then.
That's enough of the Che Guevara speech.
Tell me why you're here today.
Since you asked,
I shall speak with the utmost candor.
I was hoping you could lend me some money.
Seriously? You didn't even pay
for your last reading.
And now… you're unbelievable.
How much do you need?
Just a modest amount for now.
Let us start with 50 million won.
Did you say 50 million won?
Come on now. As if I would ever have
that much money just lying around.
Hold on, you do not even have
that kind of pocket change?
I hear houses cost
hundreds of millions now.
That's exactly why I rent.
You're unbelievable.
Here, you can take that
to buy yourself a meal.
Wait, hold on a minute.
No, that's the wrong one.
Gosh.
You are just as broke as I am.
I will put this to good use
and pay you back.
You're robbing a broke woman blind.
Enough about me.
Let's go back to your story.
-What story?
-About that weird woman.
That woman in a shaman's hanbok
jumped in front of your car,
showed up at your company,
predicted that attack,
and she even offered to protect you?
What do you think her deal is?
She's really getting on my nerves.
Like a splinter under my fingernail.
Paranoia.
Are you getting enough sleep these days?
You know.
I had this weird dream the other day.
Some woman appeared in it.
And she even offered to protect you?
What do you think her deal is?
She's really getting on my nerves.
Like a splinter under my fingernail.
There's a woman?
Okay, start right there.
You dare run your vile mouth
before a Senior First Rank Royal Consort!
Seize her!
She really brings those lines
to life, doesn't she?
That's what you call real acting.
Kids these days are so cookie-cutter.
They're all academy-trained.
Yes. Right.
Babe, I've been in the editing room
for 48 hours straight.
None of them has that hungry spirit.
Should I kill this bastard?
-Right?
-Yes, you bastard.
What? "You bastard"?
-Pardon?
-Have you gone insane?
My apologies, sir.
This little punk…
Your director is speaking.
Your eyes shouldn't be glazed over
like a dead fish. What's wrong with you?
Did you hear a word I just said?
Did you?
Hey. Where are you going?
Hey! Seriously?
You serious, punk?
You're staging a one-man protest.
What's your goal?
I stand here to call out
a production system
that exploits not only crew like me
but also uncredited stand-in actors,
all in the name
of a director's artistic vision.
You mentioned
you have video evidence prepared?
Right.
THE WOMEN'S KINGDOM, STAND-IN
I just uploaded it.
I will leave it to the public to judge!
Tae-woo, why aren't you answering?
Are you sick?
You better reply soon!
Oh my god! Ji-hyo!
You really need to see this.
I think this may be your friend.
What is it now? A dating rumor?
You know your stand-in
for Royal Consort Hui?
Shin Seo-ri? What about her?
They're calling it
the Royal Consort Hui Meme.
It's blowing up online.
I think it's her.
Let me see.
You dare run your vile mouth
before a Senior First Rank Royal Consort!
You! You!
You dare run your vile mouth!
You! You! You!
You! You! You! You! You!
You! Dare! You! Dare! You! Dare!
You dare run your vile mouth!
You! You! You!
You! You! You! You! You!
You!
You dare run your vile mouth!
-You dare run your vile mouth!
-You! You! You!
You! You! You! You! You!
You!
Her again?
According to our findings,
a crew member uploaded
the original video in an attempt
to expose an abusive director.
But when a YouTuber
with a million subscribers
edited the clip, it went viral.
The Planning Team suggests
we capitalize on this hype
and integrate it
into our new promotion strategy.
You want us to hire her
as our spokesperson?
Yes, we plan to tailor
the approach for each channel.
I'm scrapping that strategy.
I'm sure you're all aware
that ahead of this launch,
we've secured convertible bonds
from Kaiserman Capital
as part of their investment conditions.
Which means
we need to make an aggressive push
into the market from the start.
I suggest you report back
with a revised plan.
Such a sweet aroma.
My good man,
what do you call this confection?
They're called Doli Manjoos.
Would you like a bag?
-Here you go.
-Thank you.
GEONSAN MARKET
A taste that could shake heaven and earth.
My palate is ablaze.
Delectably sweet.
So cold!
They consume this precious ice
without a care in the world?
If I ate this carelessly in Joseon,
I would get 30 lashes of the rod,
and my buttocks would be left in tatters.
To think I can indulge
in such luxurious yakgwa
to my heart's content.
What a wonderful world to live in!
Rice cake!
You don't have money?
My goodness. Just take it.
-Thank you.
-Sure.
Did I have a hole in my pocket?
Where did it all go?
I have been possessed by a sweet demon.
In this place,
it seems even breathing
causes money to drain away.
The four-class hierarchy
should be strictly observed,
but what choice do I have?
If I wish to avoid starving,
I need to roll up my sleeves and work.
LOOKING FOR PART-TIMERS
MOGU COFFEE
Now that I have made up my mind,
there will be no shortage
of people seeking me out.
That worries me even more.
I have arrived!
You have store management experience?
I once commanded
a retinue of some 500 women.
For such minor insubordination,
a light flogging should bring them
under control in less than 30 minutes.
May I ask how old you are?
I am old enough
to have children in school.
But I remain unmarried in this life.
Excuse me?
Do you have any other skills?
Hunting down assassins.
Eradicating swindlers.
With the secret arts I have acquired
through my own study,
inducing a stomach ailment
is well within my power.
Get out of here.
Just my damn luck.
As if slow business weren't bad enough!
Go! Get out of here.
I should have you torn from limb to limb.
How dare you throw salt in my presence!
You scoundrel!
You should be begging on your knees
for forgiveness if you bump into someone.
Where is he off to in such a hurry,
bolting away like that?
Surely there must be a place
that requires my talents.
In a world this vast?
I do not doubt it.
Right?
Mr. Cha. I can already feel
this will be a hit.
In cosmetics,
your launch image is everything.
-Spokesperson?
-That is the biggest challenge.
As latecomers to herbal cosmetics,
we need aggressive marketing
to generate hype.
Oh right.
Speaking of hype,
there's that new viral one.
You must have seen it.
The possession meme.
Possession meme?
Come on, you know.
"You dare run your vile mouth!"
That Royal Consort Hui possession meme.
My friend is MJ's ad team lead,
and they're going crazy trying to find
that possessed girl's identity.
-Is that so?
-It's totally viral.
Can't you just picture it?
Have her hold a drumstick and go, "You!"
Fried chicken, sold out.
Have her hold a lipstick and go, "You!"
Lipstick, sold out.
Boom, clap, clap!
Let us see how well you do
after failing to recognize
a top-tier talent like me.
Damn it.
Damn you.
Why are you lashing out
at someone else's flyer?
I just put those up the other day.
Why are you picking a fight
with me, thief?
Cease your babbling and begone!
"Thief"?
Looks like you got rejected for a job.
With a temper like that,
who would put you on their payroll?
And what is wrong with my temper?
Why would they not hire me?
No one will hire someone who throws
tantrums when things don't go their way.
First thing, you can't be late…
Where are you running off to?
Are you going to get paid?
Stop following me!
-Stop right there!
-You stop!
-Welcome to our summer special.
-Welcome.
As you prepare for your summer vacation,
I know many of you are concerned
about arm and belly fat.
-That's right.
-Now, you can indulge
and still stay on track with your diet.
Today on our program, we have
Sriracha chicken breasts for you!
Yes, that's right. Seeing is believing.
We have mukbang hosts in the studio today.
-Let's see what they're up to.
-Shall we?
Wow.
I get to eat chicken for free
and get paid for it?
Who knew such merrymaking existed?
I can't believe you followed me here.
You're only making money because of me.
So stop bullying me
at the boarding house already.
And stop telling the others
to bang on my walls!
I wondered why you were so quick
to arrange this job for me.
You had an ulterior motive all along.
Do not worry.
I hold on to my grudges,
but I hold on to kindness even tighter.
Have you forgotten already?
I am the one who saved your life.
The least you could do
is show eternal gratitude.
You dare forsake your savior?
Oh man. "Savior"?
Unlike some people, I would never treat
my savior like a stray mutt.
You may rest easy.
-Who are you talking about?
-Just a scoundrel I know.
Let us put the past behind us
and start anew like respectable gentlemen.
Huzzah!
You miss what's right under your nose.
I thought it'd blow over quickly,
but that buzz is lasting.
The marketing team checked,
and she's been trending at the top
of portal search algorithms for two weeks.
Turns out that crazy woman wasn't a spy.
She was a hidden gem.
No point in delaying it.
Mr. Son.
You should head out.
We need to claim her first.
I'm on my way, sir.
I heard Choi discovered
a new sellout queen?
I heard she's breaking sales records.
Her aesthetic is like
"noblewoman from the Joseon era."
A kitchen knife lives
or dies by its sharpness.
Yes, that's right.
Oh, my. What's going on there?
A game-changer for the kitchen!
The undisputed king of the kitchen!
The emperor of chopping!
The pride of Korean-made knives!
The Sapphire Rose Knife!
-And just like that, it's sold out!
-That's right!
These knife skills, praised even
by the Royal Kitchen
during my palace maid days,
have not dulled since.
The Rhythm Chinese Workbook Package.
This is all you need
to master Chinese in six months.
"Even the longest journey
begins with one step."
"No one was ever full
from the first spoonful."
"One must press forward steadily,
stacking stones one by one."
That's amazing!
We're sold out!
-Sold out!
CHINESE WORKBOOK PACKAGE
SOLD OUT
Mastering the original
Romance of the Three Kingdoms
has finally paid off.
A NEW ME, A NEW START
CERONA C
That is hectopascal-level energy for you.
You were all surprised, weren't you?
That is the power packed in every bottle.
Vitality that makes you do backflips.
You must experience it for yourself.
Everyone, I'm being told
we're already sold out.
-We're sold out.
-We sold out!
-Sold out!
When it comes to nimble footwork
and quick reflexes, none can match me.
-Sold out!
ENERGY CERONA C
SOLD OUT
Where did that woman come from?
She's just an extra here for the day.
They've sold through
this quarter's entire allocation.
The calls are still coming in
even after the sold-out notice.
Contact the supplier. Get more stock.
We have to strike while the iron is hot.
Sir, Ms. Shin isn't picking up her phone.
She couldn't already be
in talks with someone else, right?
You need to hurry.
Find the "Nation's Gravel" or whatever.
We must sign her
before anyone else finds out.
Get her signature, or it'll be your head.
Yes, sir.
It won't take much time.
You might as well do one more
since you're here anyway.
Absolutely not.
It is already past the agreed-upon time.
I read in the paper
that overwork is the shortcut
to every ailment known to man.
Then I'll double your hourly wage.
Double? We should do it.
You treated me like some lowly maid
in the beginning.
It appears you have
finally recognized my worth.
In that case…
-Seven times.
-What?
For seven times the pay,
I shall gladly oblige.
Wait, what?
Are you nuts? Don't push it.
We're not in a gambling den.
Don't try to hit the jackpot here.
No more, no less. Exactly seven times.
I mean, come on. Seven times the rate is--
If you do not like it, look elsewhere.
Wait. Hold on.
Deal. Let's do it.
Wait. That worked?
Jesus.
I feel like I've seen her
somewhere before.
Where was it?
You can find black goat extract documented
even in the Annals of the Joseon Dynasty.
They say it was also the secret
to King Anjong's longevity.
The timing could not be better.
My vitality has worn considerably thin
from this compulsory fasting.
Looks like I will restore
my strength for free.
You'll probably recognize her.
She was recently crowned
the mukbang goddess.
Shall we find out what she thinks
about our black goat extract?
I'm with the mukbang goddess here.
This is perfect
for when you're feeling fatigued
and need an energy boost.
Here we go.
Oh, my.
Medicine that's good for you
often has a bitter aroma.
At times like this,
it's best to just gulp it down in one go.
One big gulp.
Hear me. Bring forth the poison.
Let go!
-Take it away!
-Oh no.
As you can see, taking care
of your health is never easy.
It requires patience.
Please don't hang up your calls.
It tastes perfectly fine.
Because this is made
with 100% free-range black goat,
there is nothing to worry about.
Switch screens!
You just threw up on live TV.
Are you insane?
Are you trying to get me fired?
Do you have any idea what you just did?
You must know you messed up.
"Royal Consort Hui of the Kang clan,
of the Inner Court,
has committed a heinous crime."
The villainess.
With a wicked woman
manipulating the throne…
She was disliked on a cataclysmic level.
Royal Consort Hui…
-So loud.
-Don't pretend to be sick.
-Drop the act.
-Please stop.
But that commoner's time will soon be up.
Even the heavens take heed,
now that the wicked vixen is gone.
I knew you were crazy from the start--
Shut it!
Shut that trap of yours!
My head is pounding.
"Shut my trap"? You can't be serious.
You clung to me when you needed me,
and now that I am no longer useful,
you cast me aside?
You swallow what is sweet
and spit out what is bitter.
That is what your despicable trap does!
You have gone too far, lady.
You must be insane.
-How dare you!
-Why, you little…
Damn it.
Why, you little…
Degenerate?
Found you.
Shin Seo-ri.
We must sign her
before anyone else finds out.
Get her signature, or it'll be your head.
Found you.
What are you doing here?
I came looking for you.
-Why?
-I have something to tell you.
Come with me.
You pop out of nowhere
and tell me to follow you?
Would it not be a gentleman's duty
to explain the circumstances first?
A gentleman's duty?
You know you're really weird, right?
We can talk about the details later.
How…
A kill list?
It was obtained from an attendant
of His Majesty's quarters.
ROYAL CONSORT HUI OF THE KANG CLAN
The one holding a sword to my throat…
was His Majesty.
Go in peace.
-Your Majesty.
-"Your Majesty"?
Shin Seo-ri.
What is His Majesty doing here?
Am I seeing things?
Right. I must have seen an apparition
because I was feeling so dizzy.
I must gather my wits about me.
Shin Seo-ri.
Why would you run away like that?
Why did you follow me all the way here?
I said I have something to tell you.
What?
Things look serious over there.
Are they fighting?
They're clearly not fighting.
Looks like things are about to heat up.
Ms. Shin Seo-ri.
I'd like to offer you a contract.
A contract?
You made it clear
I had nothing to offer you.
No, it turns out you do.
I need that.
And in turn, you. Desperately, even.
You
need me?
Here you are.
I've been looking everywhere for you.
That face…
He is no apparition.
What are you doing here?
Degenerate.
I am going to need you…
to be my shield for a moment.
MY ROYAL NEMESIS
Help!
Help me!
Let me out!
Let me out of here!
Help…
Please let me out.
Help me.
YEONGHWI CHAMBER
Help…
Please let me out.
They say cursed ties bind deeper
than destined ones.
When it feels off, it is best to avoid it.
It's even more pathetic than I expected.
Do not tell me you were tailing me.
Our Se-gye has a woman in his life?
Just an unknown actress. Nothing special.
What about the ad campaign?
Can we proceed with Ms. Shin?
-You were worried about me again.
-Worried? As if.
Did you dream about a woman you know?
Your first love from a past life?
"First love"? You've lost your damn mind!
Let us keep it simple.
We shall just follow our gut.
What a truly ridiculous woman.
Subtitle translation by Justin S. Kim